### **Sherry Xuan Yang**

<u>sherryxxyang@gmail.com</u> | 972-838-6228 | Dallas, TX https://xxsherryyy.netlify.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/sherry-x-yang GitHub: www.github.com/xxsherryyy

#### **Personal Profile**

Multidimensional technologist with broad technical skillset in full-stack development and data analytics. Believes in continuous research to create optimized sustainable solutions. Fluent in React, Vue and Node JavaScript frameworks. Passionate about aligning client vision and user focused front-end development to digitally transform businesses.

#### **Technical Skills**

- JavaScript, React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, SASS, Material UI, Firebase, Sequelize.js, Express, MySQL, MongoDB
- Tableau, SQL, Git, Command Line, Postman, Heroku, AWS, Azure DevOps, Adobe (XD, Photoshop, Illustrator)

  Professional Experience

# Sogeti - Associate Consultant

Jan 2019 - Present

- Digitally transformed a brick and mortar loan application experience into a web and mobile web eCommerce
  application within 6 months, and serviced 389 customers through organic leads within a week of the launch
- Collaborated in a Vue front-end and Node back-end agile environment on AWS's serverless CI/CD pipeline
- Created back-end API endpoints with AWS lambdas and integrated 3<sup>rd</sup> party API's with SOAP to REST calls
- Managed unique user accounts with Cognito and Dynamo DB, and secured with SHA and Blackbox features
- Monitored deployment and debugged code with AWS CloudWatch logs to deliver continuous business value
- Lead DevOps workshop to 28 consultants over automation and IaC with Terraform to deploy an app on AWS
- Published healthcare article read by +200 subscribers in Sogeti Blockchain Association's monthly newsletter
- Visualized workflows with VISIO to optimize the administration process with lean methodology
- Prototyped image recognition AI app with Google Vision to scan document texts for client development sales

#### **Corporate Relocation International - Relocation Consultant**

**April 2017 - July 2018** 

- Developed vendor relationship and managed concierge resources to accommodate over 9000 client requests
- Analyzed and compiled monthly reports from data tracking and vendors to deliver insightful cross functional data to senior executive
- Liaised with finance, accounting and vendor to optimize billing and reporting through UI and data redesign
- Assisted IT Manager with internal web client debugging and large dataset querying optimization in MS Access

#### Willis Towers Watson One Exchange - Customer Service Representative

August 2016 - November 2016

- Maintained client files and administrative documentation with CRM using OSC under HIPAA compliance
- Weekly performance review with supervisor to improve QA and reported goal evaluations through JIRA
- Exceeded 100% of monthly call goals and customer satisfaction by root cause analysis and assisted with customer de-escalation using call control

#### **UTDallas Biomedical Microdevices and Nanotechnology Lab - Volunteer**

February 2014 - November 2014

- Investigated research journals to understand concepts and procedures and applied them in bio-electrical engineering team projects
- Setup and performed dielectrophoretic experiments, and presented bi-monthly reports to research group
- Presented proposal of cell separation with di-electrophoresis at a medical device symposium

#### **Projects**

Rate That Dev | React | Node.js | Express | Mongoose | JSON Web Token | Passport | Axios

**July 2018** 

A developer rating system that features skill evaluation for developers and customized search function for recruiters

- Prototyped and developed MERN stack app UI utilizing Node.js and Express.js framework
- Built reusable JSX components and modal functions, and routed data values to backend Mongoose storage

### **Education**

## The University of Texas at Dallas, B.S., Molecular Biology

May 2017

Research: Characterizing drug induced apoptosis and non-invasive treatment in NSCLC using DEP

Southern Methodist University, Coding Boot Camp: Full-Stack Web Development Course

Aug 2018

### Certifications

- IBM Blockchain Essentials May 2019
- SQL Tips, Tricks and Techniques Jun 2018

AWS Solutions Architect – Jan 2020

SAFe DevOps Practitioner – Dec 2019